Uh application is working is
Healthy and uh
The idea was to build this
application
Specifically for this
Project so the idea is
simple I can safely introduce
Failures and test the entire
Monitoring so the remediation
pipeline without uh also the
Remediation pipeline without
affecting any wheel production
system
So as you can see here it's
Running everything is
healthy traffic is flowing
Normally and application is
Ready now comes the interesting
part I'm going to intentionally
Break the service by clicking in
this
Button when I click here so
recent activity cows mod enabled
1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 8 9 1 0 0 0 0
1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12 17 18
19 20 21 27 28 29 30
So this is the mission
control the dashboard that
I built manage operational
Incident so let's enter the
Console so here we can see the
message arrived
AI observation death watch demo
app
Else so he gave me two
option approve and
Reject so the summary is the
demo application in death
Is experiencing elevated error
rates with eight errors
Detected in the last monitoring
period exceeding except so
I have the option to approve and
Execute fix or
Reject now as you can see I have
two
Option one is approve the
remediation the other one is
reject
To reject it so nothing happened
Automatically so I have to
approve it to execute the
Fix so now I'm going to click
Here after the approval so we
can see here
As succeeded the status is
succeeded now it shows the
Started time when um
The workflow
Execution
Triggered so this resume is the
pause Step Functions workflow and
Here we have the ended so it
shows it's
Succeeded yes in this plot in
this dashboard we have the cost
Reporter as we can see here uh
my current cost reporter is
Seven
$7 so we have the services that
we
If the cost
So the cost tab shows the actual
AWS cost of running the
Platform it gives a clear view
of what the solution costs in
Practice as we have here all the
Date so now we're going to test
how assistant
Run book and ask him a
Question how do I
Call back a failed
deployment so let's ask him this
Question and see what he'll
say so as you can see
Here I made a I ask a
question how do I roll back a
Deployment to the runbook
assistant and here I have to
Answer how to hold back so we
can see here all the
answers so everything is